<dayData>
   <days class="java.util.ArrayList">
      <day d="0">
         <m>Every year, February 7 is celebrated as Rose Day which also marks the beginning of Valentine’s Week, a singleton could openly express his or her feelings towards another. Since different varieties of roses are used to express different sentiments, roses allowed people to make their intentions clearly known by presenting the object of their affection with a rose of a particular color.

         - A red rose is a symbol of romantic and passionate love.
         - Orange roses are a symbol of desire to get to know someone.
         - Yellow roses are a symbol of caring for someone.
         - White roses are a sign of secrecy and purity.
         - Lavender roses are a symbol of love at first sight
         - Pink roses are a symbol of thankfulness and admiration.
         </m>
      </day>
      <day d="1">
         <m>Every year 8 February is celebrated as Happy Propose Day (2013). It is the second day of the valentine’s Week. Feb 8 is the wonderful day for the lovers to propose someone whom they love so much. Love is something which can’t be compared with anything and can’t be resisted from any creature in this universe. Love is defined as affection, care and dedicated your entire life to your lover.

         	As rose day comes before the propose day, so your beloved knows your feelings already which was explained by your rose which was gifted on rose day. Now on propose day you have an opportunity to propose your love or sweetheart to be with you for the entire life. If your love accepts your proposal then she/he is ready to become your partner for the rest of the life.

         	So guys what are you waiting for?? Just propose your love today as if this opportunity will miss then may be you will never get this opportunity again. Remember?
         </m>
      </day>
      <day d="2">
         <m>February 14th of every year is globally associated with Saint Valentine's Day. It is supposed to be a period when gifts are exchanged between loved ones, and a time for showing love.

         	However, the Valentine celebration has started to give rise to the flagrant display of sexual promiscuity by the youth on that day.

         	The February 9th, Chocolate Day was therefore instituted to allow Ghanaians, and visitors alike, the opportunity to use cocoa, the nation's most significant crop export, to show love on Valentine's Day celebration. The other advantages of this idea are to celebrate the many nutritional and health benefits of cocoa.

         	The local concept of the National Chocolate Day, as a way of replacing the corrupted perception of Valentine's Day, must be supported by all well-meaning Ghanaians.
         </m>
      </day>
      <day d="3">
         <m>The name Teddy Bear comes from one of American President Theodore Roosevelt's hunting trips to Mississippi. There were several other hunters competing, and most of them had already shot something. A suite of Roosevelt's attendants, led by Holt Collier, cornered, clubbed, and tied to a willow tree an American Black Bear after a long exhausting chase with hounds. They called Roosevelt to the site and suggested he shoot it. He refused to shoot the bear himself, deeming this unsportsmanlike, but instructed that the bear be killed to put it out of its misery, and it became the topic of a political cartoon by Clifford Berryman in The Washington Post on November 16, 1902. While the initial cartoon of an adult black bear lassoed by a white handler and a disgusted Roosevelt had symbolic overtones, later issues of that and other Berryman cartoons made the bear smaller and cuter.

         	A Brooklyn store owner, Morris Michtom, saw the drawing of Roosevelt and the bear cub and was inspired to create a new toy. He created a little stuffed bear cub and put it in his shop window with a sign that read "Teddy's bear." The toys were an immediate success and Michtom founded the Ideal Novelty.

         	There is an occasional reference to Teddy Day on February 10 but nothing in stone. We found no factual information about this special day. We believe this is for promotion of bear products for retail purposes.
         </m>
      </day>
      <day d="4">
         <m>The promise day is one of important day of year in the life of couples and lovers. The promise day is celebrated after the sweet Chocolate Day on 11th of Feb in every year. This day is celebrated every year on Valentine week special. This day is celebrated to maintain your love in through out the lifetime by promising your partners on the special occasion of Promise Day. The Promise day is celebrated for giving a true promise to your partners like you will always care and love them and provide the best and enjoyable life to partners.

         	All lovers and couples can celebrate the Promise Day by giving a true promise to your partners. This day will provide a true and healthy relationship in your life. You can give and take a promise like always love you and care about you at every moment of life, provide a good and happy life, always help in your all problems and always keep you in my heart and many other promises which will provide a good life with your partners.

         	Use the awesome stuffs we provide to celebrate your Promise Day, February 11, and impress your partner.
         </m>
      </day>
      <day d="5">
         <m>Every year Hug Day falls on 12 February, 2013 which is a day to show your love.  Hug is the real sign of showing your endless love towards your friends, mates, beloved and your relatives.

         	Hug day is meant not only for the love birds but even for those who have parted ways. You can once again patch up with your ex on this day by hugging them and forget all your grief’s and sorrows and spending the rest of valentine week with one another.
         	Great personality said that “Hug Day is not how long you have been together; not how much you have given or receive; Not how many times you have helped each other – It’s how u value each other.”

         	Hug is used as a sign of affection. It is the best way to present your love, care and passion towards them. Hug is also used as a means of expressing importance of your loved ones in your life and makes them feel on top of the world.

         	On this Hug Day wish your beloved Happy Hug Day and hug tightly your beloved and make them feel special.
         </m>
      </day>
      <day d="6">
         <m>February 13th, it's Kiss Day! Its a day when you can kiss anyone you want and not get in trouble, a day to let your lips say how much you love your sweetheart, a day to get musshy with your love and express what he/she means to you!
         	
         	Health benefits of kissing:
         	1. Kissing Is Good For Your Teeth, there's a reason a kiss is called a "wet one" -- smooching stimulates saliva production, which can actually wash harmful bacteria off the teeth. 

         	2. Kissing Burns Calories, okay, so we're not talking the equivalent of a trip to the gym, but hey, every little bit counts, right? Locking lips can burn anywhere from two to six calories a minute. 

         	3. Kissing Boosts Immunity, there's no denying the fact that when you lock lips, there are bound to be some germs, uh, exchanged. One specific bug can be particularly hazardous to pregnant women, but researchers believe kissing is a way to introduce the virus to a woman in small doses before she conceives, triggering her body to build up a resistance to it before she could ever pass it on to a child.

         	4. Kissing Eases Stress, that feeling of relaxation post-kiss isn't all in your head. A small 2009 study reported, both men and women experienced a decline in cortisol, a sign of relaxation, that was much greater than when they just held hands.

         	So, this kiss day, kiss your reflection in the mirror, kiss someone with ice in your mouth, kiss someone with your eyes open, tell someone to just “shut up and kiss” you, kiss a baby.
         </m>
      </day>
      <day d="7">
         <m>The history of Valentine's Day, legend says, originated during the third century in Rome. During this time, Emperor Claudius II decided that single men made better soldiers, so he outlawed marriage for young men. A young priest named Valentine was furious with this injustice and defied Claudius by continuing to perform marriages for young lovers in secret. Claudius eventually discovered Valentine's actions and sentenced him to death.
            
            During his time in jail, Valentine fell in love with his jailer's daughter, who visited him in prison. Before he was put to death, Valentine sent a letter to the girl and signed it, "From Your Valentine" — an expression we still use today. Valentine was executed on February 14, 270 AD. Later, around 496 AD, Pope Gelasius declared Feb 14 a day to honor Valentine, who by that time had become a saint.

         	Today, we continue to honor St. Valentine and recall the history of Valentine's Day each year on February 14 by celebrating our love for significant others, friends, and family.
         </m>
      </day>
   </days>
</dayData>