<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<textData>

	<texts class="java.util.ArrayList">

		<t d="0">

			<m>With this rose, I reveal all my
thoughts and feelings about you
that I have withheld for so long.
I feel when I am with youŊI am like
a rose,not because of its beauty,
but because I am able to bloom and
grow with you...
Happy Rose Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>A rose doesn't means for proposing love
It also means
R- Rare
O- Ones
S- Supporting
E- Entire life
Happy Rose Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>A rose doesn't means for proposing love
It also means
R- Rare
O- Ones
S- Supporting
E- Entire life
Happy Rose Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>With this rose, I reveal all my
thoughts and feelings about you
that I have withheld for so long.
I feel when I am with youŊI am like
a rose,not because of its beauty,
but because I am able to bloom and
grow with you...
Happy Rose Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Every bird cannot dance
but PEACOCK do it..
Every friend can not
reach my heart
but YOU did it..
Every Flower can not express love
But
ROSE do it..

Happy Rose Day, Love..!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Anyone can love a Rose but
No one will love a leaf that made the
Rose.
Dont love someone who is beautiful
but love the one who can make
your life beatiful.
Happy Rose Day..!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>It happened to me.
It happened to you.
People call is love.
I call it
divine.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Each time I think of you,
I wonder what good I did,
to get a person
as wonderful as you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>The world is so beautiful.
I never knew until I met you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Seasons come and go,
days and nights alter,
but what remains with me
always is your love that never changes.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Everywhere I go,
your love spreads its wings and touches me.
Thank
you dear Valentine for binding me and yet making me free.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Darkness has left,
light is here to stay for you are with me and
the night is away.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Love is magic.
Love is fun.
Which fool would know that until he
falls in love.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>What is heaven?
I never knew until you walk in,
open your arms,
give
a hug and say those golden words.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>It's so pure.
It's so true.
For nothing more divine could God
produce than love from you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>You are away yet so close like the shadow that I chose.
Happy
Valentine's Day sweetheart!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>You are my voice,
the beat of my heart.
You are the light my eyes.
What would I do without you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Like the touch of a feather,
like the warmth of the sun,
you touched
my heart and kissed my soul.
O' Valentine! You are my life.
What would
I do without you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>If you ask me what love is, I would say I don't know. If you ask
what
heaven is, I would say I don't know. But, if you ask me what you
are
to me, I would say that you are that someone who knows me, who
gives
me a reason to breathe, gives me an excuse to pray and helps me
to
find me.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>I know I am right.
I just know it.
For you are the one.
My only
sweetheart.
I love you so and I will do so,
as life is short and you
are special.
Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Love is special and needs expression.
Don't worry anymore if you
can't express your feelings to your beloved.
Let the Valentine's Day
love messages convey your heart's feelings
in the way you want.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>You don't marry someone you can live with - you marry the person
who
you cannot live without.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>Q: Why did the boy have his girlfriend put in jail?
A: She stole
his heart.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="0">

			<m>This is to say that
I love you from the core of me heart.
I need you
and cant think of my life without you!!</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="1">

			<m>There is never a time or place for true love. It happens
accidentally, in
a heartbeat, in a single flashing, throbbing moment.
Happy Propose
Day!</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="1">

			<m>In this world, it is too common for people to search for someone
to
lose themselves in. But I am already lost... I will look for
someone
to find myself in. Happy Propose Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>If I reached for your hand, will you hold it? If I hold out my
arms,
will you hug me? If I go for ur lips, will you kiss me? If I
capture
ur heart, will you love me?? Happy Propose Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>On this special day I want to say: Grow old along with me, The
best is
yet to be. Will you spend The rest of your life with me?</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>If you wake up one day and were asked to have a wish, what would
it
be? Mine would be that our love would last until you see an apple
in
an orange tree.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>Q: How did the telephone propose to his girlfriend? A: He gave her
a
ring.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>Every day I miss you, Every night I miss you, Till when do you
want to
stay a miss, Marry me.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>I know I am right. I just know it. For you are the one. My only
sweetheart. I love you so and I will do so, as life is short and you
are special. Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>Love is special and needs expression. Don't worry anymore if you
can't
express your feelings to your beloved. Let the Valentine's Day
love
messages convey your heart's feelings in the way you want.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="1">

			<m>You don't marry someone you can live with - you marry the person
who
you cannot live without.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>Q: Why did the boy have his girlfriend put in jail? A: She stole
his
heart.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>This is to say that I love you from the core of me heart. I need
you and
cant think of my life without you!!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>They say you can do anything for love, but for you I'd do even
more.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>Some people believe in God, Some don't, I believe in you, I love
you</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>God made woman beautiful and foolish; beautiful, that man might
love
her; and foolish, that she might love him.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>Day or night... i always think of you.... can't escape the feeling
of
how i'm into you... as much as i love you...i hope you know what
you
mean to me!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>My heart is so intertwined with your heart, that it stops beating
when
we are apart.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="1">

			<m>Looking at our kids, I realize how far we've come. We have been
through a
lot and yet we are still together and stronger than ever.
Thank you
for staying beside me. I love you!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>Everything comes with an expiry date. Thankfully something like
friendship,
still exists. I at least have something forever. I don't
ever want
to lose you. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>Friendship is the most beautiful word ever invented. One may even
lose love at
some point of time in life, but a true friend will be by
your side
forever. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>I can tell you everything under the sun. I can have the most
awesome
time with you, even when we are just freaking out. When I
look back
it makes me realize that, you are the most amazing part of
each and
every day of mine. I love you. Happy Valentines day my
friend.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="1">

			<m>It happened to me. It happened to you. People call is love. I call
it
divine.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="1">

			<m>When you feel cold and warm at the same time, when you read over
the
same line for the tenth time, when your heart and thoughts
somehow
appear to rhyme, nd when a simple name conquers your whole
mind,
then you are in deep trouble my friend You are LOVE, We call it
the
hard time !!</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="2">

			<m>Love Is Like Dark Chocolate Although It Always Leaves You With A Bitter
Taste In Your Mouth, You Will Still Be Tempted To Take A Bite The
Next Time Around. Happy Chocolate Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>This is a chocolate message, For a dairy milk person, From a five star
friend, For a melody reason, And a kitkat time, On a munch day, In a
perk mood to say, Happy Chocolate Day..</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>I Searched Many Shops To Buy D Best Chocolate 4 U. But I Didn't Find
Any Chocolate Sweeter Than U and Ur Smile.. Happy Chocolate Day..</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>Love is like a chewing gum, it tastes only in the beginning! But
friendship is like chocolate, it tastes till it ends! Happy
Chocolate Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>The world is so beautiful. I never knew until I met you.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="2">

			<m>Seasons come and go, days and nights alter, but what remains with me always
is your love that never changes.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>Everywhere I go, your love spreads its wings and touches me. Thank you dear
Valentine for binding me and yet making me free.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>Darkness has left, light is here to stay for you are with me and the night
is away.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>Love is magic. Love is fun. Which fool would know that until he falls in
love.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>What is heaven? I never knew until you walk in, open your arms, give a
hug and say those golden words.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>It's so pure. It's so true. For nothing more divine could God produce
than love from you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>You are away yet so close like the shadow that I chose. Happy
Valentine's Day sweetheart!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>You are my voice, the beat of my heart. You are the light my eyes. What
would I do without you.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="2">

			<m>Like the touch of a feather, like the warmth of the sun, you touched my
heart and kissed my soul. O Valentine! You are my life. What would I
do without you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>If you ask me what love is, I would say I don't know. If you ask what
heaven is, I would say I don't know. But, if you ask me what you are
to me, I would say that you are that someone who knows me, who gives
me a reason to breathe, gives me an excuse to pray and helps me to
find me.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>I know I am right. I just know it. For you are the one. My only
sweetheart. I love you so and I will do so, as life is short and you
are special. Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>Love is special and needs expression. Don't worry anymore if you can't
express your feelings to your beloved. Let the Valentine's Day love
messages convey your heart's feelings in the way you want.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>You don't marry someone you can live with - you marry the person who
you cannot live without.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>Q: Why did the boy have his girlfriend put in jail? A: She stole his
heart.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>This is to say that I love you from the core of me heart. I need you and
cant think of my life without you!!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>They say you can do anything for love, but for you I'd do even more.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>Some people believe in God, Some don't, I believe in you, I love you</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>God made woman beautiful and foolish; beautiful, that man might love
her; and foolish, that she might love him.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="2">

			<m>Day or night... i always think of you.... can't escape the feeling of
how i'm into you... as much as i love you...i hope you know what you
mean to me!</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="3">

			<m>A sweet Teddy Bear, To My sweet mate, On A sweet events, Just To Say,
Happy Teddy Bear Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>On Teddy Bear Day, We Think Of People Who Have Cheered And Encouraged
Us, Who Go Out Of Their Way To Be Kind And Caring, Who Have Enriched
Our Lives Just By Being Themselves. You Are Such A Person. I'm So
Happy You're My Love Happy Teddy Bear Day</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>On Teddy Bear Day, We Think Of People Who Have Cheered And Encouraged
Us, Who Go Out Of Their Way To Be Kind And Caring, Who Have Enriched
Our Lives Just By Being Themselves. You Are Such A Person. I'm So
Happy You're My Love Happy Teddy Bear Day</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>The world is so beautiful. I never knew until I met you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Seasons come and go, days and nights alter, but what remains with me always
is your love that never changes.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Everywhere I go, your love spreads its wings and touches me. Thank you dear
Valentine for binding me and yet making me free.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Like the touch of a feather, like the warmth of the sun, you touched my
heart and kissed my soul. O Valentine! You are my life. What would I
do without you.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="3">

			<m>If you ask me what love is, I would say I don't know. If you ask what
heaven is, I would say I don't know. But, if you ask me what you are
to me, I would say that you are that someone who knows me, who gives
me a reason to breathe, gives me an excuse to pray and helps me to
find me.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>I know I am right. I just know it. For you are the one. My only
sweetheart. I love you so and I will do so, as life is short and you
are special. Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Love is special and needs expression. Don't worry anymore if you can't
express your feelings to your beloved. Let the Valentine's Day love
messages convey your heart's feelings in the way you want.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>You don't marry someone you can live with - you marry the person who
you cannot live without.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Q: Why did the boy have his girlfriend put in jail? A: She stole his
heart.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Darkness has left, light is here to stay for you are with me and the night
is away.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Love is magic. Love is fun. Which fool would know that until he falls in
love.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>What is heaven? I never knew until you walk in, open your arms, give a
hug and say those golden words.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>It's so pure. It's so true. For nothing more divine could God produce
than love from you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>You are away yet so close like the shadow that I chose. Happy
Valentine's Day sweetheart!</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="3">

			<m>You are my voice, the beat of my heart. You are the light my eyes. What
would I do without you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>This is to say that I love you from the core of me heart. I need you and
cant think of my life without you!!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>They say you can do anything for love, but for you I'd do even more.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Looking at our kids, I realize how far we've come. We have been through a
lot and yet we are still together and stronger than ever. Thank you
for staying beside me. I love you!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Everything comes with an expiry date. Thankfully something like friendship,
still exists. I at least have something forever. I don't ever want
to lose you. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>Friendship is the most beautiful word ever invented. One may even lose love at
some point of time in life, but a true friend will be by your side
forever. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="3">

			<m>I can tell you everything under the sun. I can have the most awesome
time with you, even when we are just freaking out. When I look back
it makes me realize that, you are the most amazing part of each and
every day of mine. I love you. Happy Valentines day my friend.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="4">

			<m>I Must Have Been Born Under A Lucky Star, To Find A Friend As Nice As
You Are. I Will Follow The Rainbow To The End , If You Promise To
Remain My Friend !!! Happy Promise Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>I Don't Promise You The Moon, I Don't Promise You The Star, But If
You Promise To Remember Me, I Promise To Be Always There. Happy
Promise Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>We Have So Much More Than I Ever Thought We Would, I Love You More
Than I Ever Thought I Could. I Promise To Give You All I Have To
Give, I'll Do Anything For You As Long As I Live. Happy Promise day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>Friendship is a language spoken by heart, Not written on paper, Not given by
pledge, It is a promise on this Promise Day, To renewed every time
we keep in touch.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>I love you. You complete my heart, my soul and my life. I will always
love you, come what may. You are the joy in my laughter and oxygen
in every breath. Dont ever forget me.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>Like the touch of a feather, like the warmth of the sun, you touched my
heart and kissed my soul. O Valentine! You are my life. What would I
do without you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>If you ask me what love is, I would say I don't know. If you ask what
heaven is, I would say I don't know. But, if you ask me what you are
to me, I would say that you are that someone who knows me, who gives
me a reason to breathe, gives me an excuse to pray and helps me to
find me.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>I know I am right. I just know it. For you are the one. My only
sweetheart. I love you so and I will do so, as life is short and you
are special. Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>Love is special and needs expression. Don't worry anymore if you can't
express your feelings to your beloved. Let the Valentine's Day love
messages convey your heart's feelings in the way you want.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>You don't marry someone you can live with - you marry the person who
you cannot live without.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="4">

			<m>Q: Why did the boy have his girlfriend put in jail? A: She stole his
heart.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>This is to say that I love you from the core of me heart. I need you and
cant think of my life without you!!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>They say you can do anything for love, but for you I'd do even more.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>Some people believe in God, Some don't, I believe in you, I love you</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>God made woman beautiful and foolish; beautiful, that man might love
her; and foolish, that she might love him.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>Day or night... i always think of you.... can't escape the feeling of
how i'm into you... as much as i love you...i hope you know what you
mean to me!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>My heart is so intertwined with your heart, that it stops beating when
we are apart.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>When you feel cold and warm at the same time, when you read over the
same line for the tenth time, when your heart and thoughts somehow
appear to rhyme, nd when a simple name conquers your whole mind,
then you are in deep trouble my friend You are LOVE, We call it the
hard time !!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>Looking at our kids, I realize how far we've come. We have been through a
lot and yet we are still together and stronger than ever. Thank you
for staying beside me. I love you!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>Everything comes with an expiry date. Thankfully something like friendship,
still exists. I at least have something forever. I don't ever want
to lose you. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>Friendship is the most beautiful word ever invented. One may even lose love at
some point of time in life, but a true friend will be by your side
forever. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>My Dear Husband, Every love story is beautiful, but ours is my
favorite. Happy Valentines!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>God made woman beautiful and foolish; beautiful, that man might love
her; and foolish, that she might love him.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="4">

			<m>Day or night... i always think of you.... can't escape the feeling of
how i'm into you... as much as i love you...i hope you know what you
mean to me!</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="5">

			<m>I will just pretend to hug you until you get here... Happy Hug Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>During the lowest phase of your life A simple hug from that special
someone Can turn your tears to joy Wish You A Beautiful and Joyful Hug
Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>A simple hug from the one you love is the biggest satisfication in
the world.. because you know you are in the right place even when
everything else is wrong..</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="5">

			<m>Love is magic. Love is fun. Which fool would know that until he falls in
love.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>What is heaven? I never knew until you walk in, open your arms, give a
hug and say those golden words.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>It's so pure. It's so true. For nothing more divine could God produce
than love from you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>You are away yet so close like the shadow that I chose. Happy
Valentine's Day sweetheart!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>You are my voice, the beat of my heart. You are the light my eyes. What
would I do without you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>Like the touch of a feather, like the warmth of the sun, you touched my
heart and kissed my soul. O Valentine! You are my life. What would I
do without you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>If you ask me what love is, I would say I don't know. If you ask what
heaven is, I would say I don't know. But, if you ask me what you are
to me, I would say that you are that someone who knows me, who gives
me a reason to breathe, gives me an excuse to pray and helps me to
find me.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>I know I am right. I just know it. For you are the one. My only
sweetheart. I love you so and I will do so, as life is short and you
are special. Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>Love is special and needs expression. Don't worry anymore if you can't
express your feelings to your beloved. Let the Valentine's Day love
messages convey your heart's feelings in the way you want.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>You don't marry someone you can live with - you marry the person who
you cannot live without.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>Q: Why did the boy have his girlfriend put in jail? A: She stole his
heart.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="5">

			<m>This is to say that I love you from the core of me heart. I need you and
cant think of my life without you!!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>They say you can do anything for love, but for you I'd do even more.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>Some people believe in God, Some don't, I believe in you, I love you</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>God made woman beautiful and foolish; beautiful, that man might love
her; and foolish, that she might love him.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>Day or night... i always think of you.... can't escape the feeling of
how i'm into you... as much as i love you...i hope you know what you
mean to me!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>My heart is so intertwined with your heart, that it stops beating when
we are apart.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>When you feel cold and warm at the same time, when you read over the
same line for the tenth time, when your heart and thoughts somehow
appear to rhyme, nd when a simple name conquers your whole mind,
then you are in deep trouble my friend You are LOVE, We call it the
hard time !!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>Looking at our kids, I realize how far we've come. We have been through a
lot and yet we are still together and stronger than ever. Thank you
for staying beside me. I love you!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>Everything comes with an expiry date. Thankfully something like friendship,
still exists. I at least have something forever. I don't ever want
to lose you. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="5">

			<m>Friendship is the most beautiful word ever invented. One may even lose love at
some point of time in life, but a true friend will be by your side
forever. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="6">

			<m>When you kiss me without uttering a single word, you speak to my soul..
Happy Kiss Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>The kiss is the passionate desire of one soul to cling to another. At
the break of each and every kiss the soul plants an eternal essence
of that person deep within the memory of your heart. And you possess
a tiny part of that person's soul forever.... Happy Kiss Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>Happiness is like a kiss It feels best when you Give it to someone else!
Happy Kiss Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>Love is magic. Love is fun. Which fool would know that until he falls in
love.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>What is heaven? I never knew until you walk in, open your arms, give a
hug and say those golden words.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>It's so pure. It's so true. For nothing more divine could God produce
than love from you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>You are away yet so close like the shadow that I chose. Happy
Valentine's Day sweetheart!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>You are my voice, the beat of my heart. You are the light my eyes. What
would I do without you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>Like the touch of a feather, like the warmth of the sun, you touched my
heart and kissed my soul. O Valentine! You are my life. What would I
do without you.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>If you ask me what love is, I would say I don't know. If you ask what
heaven is, I would say I don't know. But, if you ask me what you are
to me, I would say that you are that someone who knows me, who gives
me a reason to breathe, gives me an excuse to pray and helps me to
find me.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>I know I am right. I just know it. For you are the one. My only
sweetheart. I love you so and I will do so, as life is short and you
are special. Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>Love is special and needs expression. Don't worry anymore if you can't
express your feelings to your beloved. Let the Valentine's Day love
messages convey your heart's feelings in the way you want.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>You don't marry someone you can live with - you marry the person who
you cannot live without.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="6">

			<m>Q: Why did the boy have his girlfriend put in jail? A: She stole his
heart.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>This is to say that I love you from the core of me heart. I need you and
cant think of my life without you!!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>They say you can do anything for love, but for you I'd do even more.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>Looking at our kids, I realize how far we've come. We have been through a
			lot and yet we are still together and stronger than ever. Thank you
for staying beside me. I love you!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>Everything comes with an expiry date. Thankfully something like friendship,
still exists. I at least have something forever. I don't ever want
to lose you. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>Friendship is the most beautiful word ever invented. One may even lose love at
some point of time in life, but a true friend will be by your side
forever. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>I can tell you everything under the sun. I can have the most awesome\ntime with you, even when we are just freaking out. When I look back
it makes me realize that, you are the most amazing part of each and
every day of mine. I love you. Happy Valentines day my friend.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>Some people believe in God, Some don't, I believe in you, I love you</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>God made woman beautiful and foolish; beautiful, that man might love
her; and foolish, that she might love him.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>Day or night... i always think of you.... can't escape the feeling of
how i'm into you... as much as i love you...i hope you know what you
mean to me!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="6">

			<m>My heart is so intertwined with your heart, that it stops beating when
we are apart.</m>
		</t>
		
		<t d="7">

			<m>No words can tell you How I love you Yet I try again To use them In
the right way For you are the best And you must know this I love you
so much And I love you for this Happy Valentine's Day dear
boyfriend!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Days have passed Months have gone by Making me love you more With every
moment that goes by Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>The twinkle in your eyes The spark in your words Passes a current
through me Which I would never hide.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>When I am low You stand like a rock When I cry You hold every drop What
would I do without you O darling you mean the world to me Happy
Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>This Valentine's Day I have to confess No matter how much we find How
much ever you tease me How much you annoy me I can't do without you
Happy Valentine's Day dear boyfriend!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>You are like the blessing from heaven So sweet and so pure You are the
breathe I take, the music I hear For, you are not just my boyfriend
You are My Life! Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>My life was in a shell So dark, so lonely Until you came in And filled
my life with joy I love you for this dear boyfriend And for reasons
still unknown to me. Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>I never knew what heaven was Until I met you and fell in love I am in
heaven every single moment That I spend in your arms And feel the
bliss every breathe I take. Happy Valentine's Day darling!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Is love a magic I often thought I met the magician Who said its not
But enchanted me for life And made a spell on me That I am still
into The magic of love The magic by you! Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>It makes me proud To be your girlfriend And be with the person I truly
love and admire. Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>My life was an empty canvass You filled it with colors Some from the
rainbow And some from the butterflies Making it a canvass so
precious So wanted, so blessed and so live Thank you dear boyfriend
Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>*@'''''''@* ** ( ' ; ' )** *(@)-""-(@)* *(@)(@)* Here is a chota sa, mota sa
teddy bear 4 U! Happy Valentines day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>_____****__________**** ______ ___***____***____***__ *** ____
__***________****________***____ _***__________**__________***__
_***____HEART_FULL_OF__ ***_ _***________LOVE_________***_
__***____________________***___ ___***__________________***____
____***_______________***_____ ______***___________***_______
________***_______***_________ __________***___***___________
____________*****_____________ _____________***_____________
______________*_____________ Happy Valentines Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>I wanted to tell you that wherever I am, whatever happens, I'll
always think of you, and the time we spent together, as my happiest
time. I'd do it all over again, if I had the choice. Happy
Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>I have tried to let you go and I cannot. I cannot stop thinking of
you. I cannot stop dreaming about you. I love you my Valentine!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>When you truly love someone.. You give everything, You never expect a
return... Happy Valentines Day My Sweetheart!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Lovers don't finally meet somewhere. They're in each other all along...
Happy Valentine's Day My Love...!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Hum Apne Aap Pe Garoor Nahi Karte.... Kisi ko pyar karne pe majboor
nahi karte.... Magar jise aik baar dil main basa liya.... Phir marte
dam tak ussy dil se dour nahi karte. Happy Valentines Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Jante ho sab fir bhi anjaan bante ho. Is tarah aap hume pareshan karte
ho. Puchte ho ki kya pasand hai apko. Khud jawaab hokar ye sawal
karte ho! Happy Valentines Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>, -. .- , -. .- . '. ...I...L ..U...' "" . "" """" . "" I FEEL U THIS
WAY be my Valentine.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Love puts the fun in together, the sad in apart, and the joy in a heart.
Happy Valentine's Day my love.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>We're two parts of a loving whole Two hearts and a single soul</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Thinking of you! Dreaming of You! Hugging you! Missing you! Wishing you! I
Love You! Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>On Valentine's Day we think of those Who make our lives worthwhile,
Those gracious, friendly people who We think of with a smile. I am
fortunate to know you, That's why I want to say, To a rare and
special person: Happy Valentine's Day</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>What i need to live has been given to me by the earth.. Why i need to
live has been given to me by you my valentine !!! Happy Valentines
Day</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>No poems no fancy words I just want the world to know that I LOVE YOU
my Princess with all my heart. Happy Valentines Day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Don't wait until it's too late to tell someone how much you love, how
much you care. Because when they're gone, no matter how loud you
shout and cry, they won't hear you anymore. Happy Valentine's Day</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>I have liked many but loved very few.yet no-one has been as sweet as
you. I'd stand and wait in the worlds longest queue. Just for the
pleasure of a moment with you. Happy Valentines Day my Love!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Mesmerize me in your tender love and care, Staring in the eyes of sumone so
rare, That special feeling I cant bear, Wenever you want me i'll
always be there. Happy Valentines Day....!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Your eyes, your smile. Your touch, your kiss. Your promise, your words.
Our everlasting bliss. Happy Valentine Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Your love surrounds me like the air that I breathe. Your kiss touches me
as gentle as a breeze. Your touch is as tender as that of a child.
Your hug is warm, meek, and mild. Each day we grow older and its
plain to see, The love that you give me is all that I need. Happy
Valentine Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>You are more than love to me... You are everything. Happy Valentine
Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>I love your dark eyes, And your curly hair, I love your smile, And
the way that you care. I love your deep kisses, I love your soft
touch, I love you, I love you, I love you so much. Happy Valentine
Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>I asked God for a flower, he gave me a bouquet I asked God for a
minute, he gave me a day I asked God for true love, he gave me that
too I asked for an angel and he gave me you. Happy Valentine Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>You kissed my lips and I felt a flutter in my heart, You touched my
hand and lit a spark in my body, You stared into my eyes and saw
straight into my soul, You put your arms around me and I was finally
complete. Happy Valentine Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>To all my friends who are committed: Happy Valentine's Day... And also
To all my friends who r single, Happy Independence Life.:-)</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>I may not be as sweet you want me to be. I may not always say how
much I love you. I may not give you hugs and kisses as much as you
do. But that doesn't matter because God knows how much you mean so
much to me. You are the best gift I got from Him. Happy Valentine's
Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Today I want you to know that I love you dearly. Years spent with you
shall be memories that will be cherished not just remembered. Happy
Valentine's Day to you sweetheart!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>I have a new tattoo. It is your name beautifully carved in my heart.
Happy Valentine's Day!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>You have given me strength when I am weak, made me smile when I am sad.
You showered me with love when I needed it the most. I love you for
always bringing out the best in me. Happy Valentine's Day to you!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>It's magic each time we hold each other, each time we cuddle, and each
time we kiss. I feel goosebumps all over again. I never want to let
you go for fear of losing you, so I just hold on a little bit
tighter each day, refusing to let go. Happy Valentine's Day dear
Husband!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>My Dear Husband, Every love story is beautiful, but ours is my
favorite. Happy Valentines!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>God made woman beautiful and foolish; beautiful, that man might love
her; and foolish, that she might love him.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Day or night... i always think of you.... can't escape the feeling of
how i'm into you... as much as i love you...i hope you know what you
mean to me!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>My heart is so intertwined with your heart, that it stops beating when
we are apart.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>When you feel cold and warm at the same time, when you read over the
same line for the tenth time, when your heart and thoughts somehow
appear to rhyme, nd when a simple name conquers your whole mind,
then you are in deep trouble my friend You are LOVE, We call it the
hard time !!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Looking at our kids, I realize how far we've come. We have been through a
lot and yet we are still together and stronger than ever. Thank you
for staying beside me. I love you!</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Everything comes with an expiry date. Thankfully something like friendship,
still exists. I at least have something forever. I don't ever want
to lose you. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>Friendship is the most beautiful word ever invented. One may even lose love at
some point of time in life, but a true friend will be by your side
forever. Happy Valentines day.</m>
		</t>

		<t d="7">

			<m>I can tell you everything under the sun. I can have the most awesome
time with you, even when we are just freaking out. When I look back
it makes me realize that, you are the most amazing part of each and
every day of mine. I love you. Happy Valentines day my friend.</m>
		</t>
		
	</texts>

</textData>